Merrimack Films records 7064
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III. Audiovisual Materials, 1973-2007
  - III.d. U-matic
    - Unions in Crisis: National Archives A, 1989-12; Umatic (Box 24, Item 9)
      7 videos. Film Transfer Master.
    - Unions in Crisis: National Archives B, 1990-07-23; Umatic (Box 24, Item 10)
      5 videos.
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; Umatic (Box 24, Item 11)
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; Umatic (Box 24, Item 12)
    - The Unemployed: National Archives #1, 1987-06-04; Umatic (Box 24, Item 13)
      4 videos. Archival film transfer.
    - The Unemployed, Undated; Umatic (Box 24, Item 14)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; Umatic (Box 24, Item 15)
  - III.e. VHS
    - Labor Notes Biennial Conference, 1999-04-25; VHS (Box 2, Item 1)
      April 23-25, 1999.
    - Fast Track Victory Celebration, 1998-04-18; VHS (Box 2, Item 2)
    - SMA Class of 1953 Reunion, Undated; VHS (Box 2, Item 3)
    - They'll Never Keep Us Down, Undated; VHS (Box 2, Item 14)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1992; VHS (Box 3, Item 24)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1992; VHS (Box 3, Item 25)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; VHS (Box 3, Item 26)
    - Union Democracy, 1986; VHS (Box 3, Item 27)
    - Union Democracy, 1986; VHS (Box 3, Item 28)
    - Union Democracy, 1986; VHS (Box 3, Item 29)
    - Union Democracy, 1986; VHS (Box 3, Item 30)
    - Union Democracy, 1986; VHS (Box 3, Item 31)
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; VHS (Box 4, Item 1)
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; VHS (Box 4, Item 2)
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; VHS (Box 4, Item 3)
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; VHS (Box 4, Item 4)
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; VHS (Box 4, Item 5)
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; VHS (Box 4, Item 6)
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; VHS (Box 4, Item 7)
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; VHS (Box 4, Item 8)
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; VHS (Box 4, Item 9)
      VCTM 356-#2
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; VHS (Box 4, Item 10)
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; VHS (Box 4, Item 11)
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; VHS (Box 4, Item 12)
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; VHS (Box 4, Item 13)
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; VHS (Box 4, Item 14)
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; VHS (Box 4, Item 15)
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; VHS (Box 4, Item 16)
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1978; VHS (Box 4, Item 17)
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1978; VHS (Box 4, Item 18)
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1978; VHS (Box 4, Item 19)
      VCTM 60-#2
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1978; VHS (Box 4, Item 20)
      VCTM 60-#3
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1978; VHS (Box 4, Item 21)
      VCTM 60-#5
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1978; VHS (Box 4, Item 22)
      VCTM 60-#6
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1978; VHS (Box 4, Item 23)
      VCTM 60-#7
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1978; VHS (Box 4, Item 24)
      VCTM 60-#8
    - Taxes, Taxes, 1978; VHS (Box 4, Item 25)
      VCTM 60-#1
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; VHS (Box 4, Item 26)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; VHS (Box 4, Item 27)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; VHS (Box 4, Item 28)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; VHS (Box 4, Item 29)
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; VHS (Box 4, Item 30)
    - Sparrows Point, Reels 1-4, Undated; VHS (Box 6, Item 1)
      Burn-in Dub
    - Sparrows Point, Reels 5-8, Undated; VHS (Box 6, Item 2)
    - Sparrows Point, Reels 9-10, Undated; VHS (Box 6, Item 3)
    - Sparrows Point, Reels 11-14, 1996-02-19; VHS (Box 6, Item 4)
      Window Burn Ins
    - Sparrows Point, Reels 1-4, Undated; VHS (Box 6, Item 5)
    - Sparrows Point, Reels 5-8, Undated; VHS (Box 6, Item 6)
    - Sparrows Point, Reels 9-10, Undated; VHS (Box 6, Item 7)
    - Sparrows Point, Reels 11-14, 1996-02-19; VHS (Box 6, Item 8)
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; VHS (Box 6, Item 9)
      VCTM 350-#1
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; VHS (Box 6, Item 10)
      VCTM 350-#4
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; VHS (Box 6, Item 11)
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; VHS (Box 6, Item 12)
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; VHS (Box 6, Item 13)
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; VHS (Box 6, Item 14)
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; VHS (Box 6, Item 15)
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; VHS (Box 6, Item 16)
    - Unions in Crisis, 1992; VHS (Box 6, Item 17)
    - WQED's Remaking Cities, Undated; VHS (Box 7, Item 10)
      Burn-in Dub from 1" master with matching TC.
    - Ron Carey Interview, Undated; VHS (Box 7, Item 21)
    - Saturn, Spring Hill, 1994-02-28; VHS (Box 9, Item 9)
      Time Code Window. Chan 5 Tape.
    - Polaroid Series 1, Undated; VHS (Box 10, Item 1)
      Reels 3 and 4
    - Polaroid Series 1, Undated; VHS (Box 10, Item 2)
      Reels 5 through 9 (Part 1)
    - Polaroid Series 1, Undated; VHS (Box 10, Item 3)
      Reels 9 and 10, TC Window.
    - Troubles at Polaroid, 1997-09-17; VHS (Box 10, Item 4)
      Reels 20 through 22. TC window dubs from field tapes.
    - Troubles at Polaroid, 1997-09-17; VHS (Box 10, Item 5)
      Reels 23 through 25. TC window dubs from field tapes.
    - Troubles at Polaroid, 1997-09-17; VHS (Box 10, Item 6)
      Reels 26 plus Polaroid footage. TC window dubs.
    - Merrimack Films Akron Ohio, Undated; VHS (Box 10, Item 7)
      Tapes 14-15. Time code window.
    - Merrimack Films Tommy Powell, Undated; VHS (Box 10, Item 8)
      Reels 41-42. TC window.
    - Merrimack Films, Undated; VHS (Box 10, Item 9)
      Reels 43-44.
    - Merrimack Films, Undated; VHS (Box 10, Item 10)
      Reels 45-46.
    - "GSU" Atlanta, 1999-05; VHS (Box 11, Item 12)
      Reels 1-4. Window dubs from Betacam 12-15
    - "GSU" Atlanta, 1999-05; VHS (Box 11, Item 13)
      Reels 5-8. Window dubs from Betacam 16-19
    - "GSU" Atlanta, 1999-05; VHS (Box 11, Item 14)
      Reels 9-12. Window dubs from Betacam 20-22, 01
    - "GSU" Atlanta, 1999-05; VHS (Box 11, Item 15)
      Reels 13-16. Window dubs from Betacam 02-05
    - "GSU" Atlanta, 1999-05; VHS (Box 11, Item 16)
      Reels 17-20. Window dubs from Betacam 06-09
    - "GSU" Atlanta, 1999-05; VHS (Box 11, Item 17)
      Reels 21-22. Window dubs from Betacam 08-10
    - Struggling Unions Summary, Undated; VHS (Box 11, Item 18)
    - Struggling Unions Summary, Undated; VHS (Box 11, Item 19)
    - Struggling Unions Summary, Undated; VHS (Box 11, Item 20)
    - Unions/NYC Footage, 1999-10; VHS (Box 11, Item 21)
      Tapes 1-4. Time Code Windows
    - Unions/NYC Footage, 1999-10; VHS (Box 11, Item 22)
      Tapes 9-12. Time Code Windows.
    - Givebacks: The UAW and the Auto Industry, 1985-06-28; VHS (Box 12, Item 11)
      VCTM 64-#1.
    - Loose Bolts?, 1985-06-28; VHS (Box 12, Item 12)
      VCTM 59-#1.
    - Sample Reel: Productions Using Stock Footage, Undated; VHS (Box 12, Item 13)
    - Rustbelt Phoenix Tape 2, Undated; VHS (Box 12, Item 15)
    - Rustbelt Phoenix Tape 3, Undated; VHS (Box 12, Item 16)
    - Rustbelt Phoenix Edited Meeting, Undated; VHS (Box 12, Item 17)
    - Camp Steel, 2005-11; VHS (Box 12, Item 18)
      miniDV
    - Rustbelt Phoenix Tin Mill Meeting, Undated; VHS (Box 12, Item 19)
      Sid's edit.
    - Sparrows Point II, 1996-03-12; VHS (Box 12, Item 20)
    - Sparrows Point B-Roll, Undated; VHS (Box 12, Item 21)
      Basic oxygen furnace; continuous slab caster; 80" hot strip mill; #4 hot dip coating lane
    - Struggling Unions: Detroit 1 and 2, 1999-04; VHS (Box 16, Item 1)
    - Struggling Unions: Detroit 3 and 4, 1999-04-26; VHS (Box 16, Item 2)
    - Struggling Unions: Detroit 5 and 6, Undated; VHS (Box 16, Item 3)
    - Struggling Unions: Detroit 7 and 8, Undated; VHS (Box 16, Item 4)
    - Struggling Unions: Detroit 9 and 10, Undated; VHS (Box 16, Item 5)
    - Struggling Unions: Detroit 11, Undated; VHS (Box 16, Item 6)
    - Struggling Unions, First Draft, Undated; VHS (Box 16, Item 30)
    - Struggling Unions, 2002; VHS (Box 16, Item 31)
      Stereo mix.
    - Eric Stier Interview, 2000-04; VHS (Box 16, Item 32)
      Tapes 1-4.
    - Unions/NYC Footage, 1999-10; VHS (Box 16, Item 33)
      Tapes 5-8. Time Code Windows
    - Unions/NYC Footage, 1999-10; VHS (Box 16, Item 34)
      Tapes 13-14. Time Code Windows.
    - Spring Hill, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 9)
    - Spring Hill, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 10)
    - Spring Hill, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 11)
    - Spring Hill, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 12)
    - Spring Hill, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 13)
    - Spring Hill, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 14)
    - Spring Hill, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 15)
      Tape #7-10
    - What Happened to Saturn, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 16)
      First cut.
    - Saturn 2: Detroit Shoot, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 17)
    - Saturn, 2007-03-30; VHS (Box 18, Item 18)
      B-Roll. New.
    - Interviews, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 19)
    - Tom Hopp and ABC News, 1998; VHS (Box 18, Item 20)
      Tom Hopp at NDM Conference, October 1998. ABC News, March 1998.
    - Interview and skit, 2006-03-16; VHS (Box 18, Item 21)
      Includes Mad TV skit
    - Spring Hill, TN, Saturn Facility Interviews, 2007-03-22; VHS (Box 18, Item 22)
    - Spring Hill, TN, Saturn Facility Interviews, 2007-03-22; VHS (Box 18, Item 23)
      Tapes 5-8.
    - Saturn, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 24)
    - Saturn 2, Summary Tape A, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 25)
    - Saturn 2, Summary Tape B, Undated; VHS (Box 18, Item 26)
    - Carpenters' Union, 1999-07-01; VHS (Box 18, Item 29)
      Tapes 1-5. Window.
    - Carpenters' Union and MIT, 1999-08-02; VHS (Box 18, Item 30)
      Tapes 1-4. Window.
    - Washington DC Interviews, 2000-05; VHS (Box 18, Item 31)
    - Washington DC Interviews, 2000-05; VHS (Box 18, Item 32)
      Tape 5. Time Code Windows
    - Boston Panel, 1992-06-24; VHS (Box 19, Item 7)
      Reels 1, 2, 3. Time code burns.
    - Jerry Tucker in Boston, 1992-04-12; VHS (Box 19, Item 8)
      Reel 1 and 2. At UAW meeting.
    - Sparrows Point, 2005-05; VHS (Box 19, Item 22)
      Reels 1 and 2. Window dubs.
    - Sparrows Point, 2005-05; VHS (Box 19, Item 23)
      Reels 3 and 4. Window dubs.
    - Sparrows Point, 2005-05; VHS (Box 19, Item 24)
      Reels 5 and 6. Window dubs.
    - Sparrows Point, 2005-05; VHS (Box 19, Item 25)
      Reels 7 and 8. Window dubs.
    - Sparrows Point, 2005-05; VHS (Box 19, Item 26)
      Reel 9. Window dubs. B-Roll.
    - Cleveland Ohio, 2005-07; VHS (Box 19, Item 27)
    - Cleveland Ohio, 2005-07; VHS (Box 19, Item 28)
    - Cleveland Ohio, 2005-07; VHS (Box 19, Item 29)
    - Cleveland Ohio, 2005-07; VHS (Box 19, Item 30)
    - Cleveland Ohio, 2005-07; VHS (Box 19, Item 31)
      Tape #5. B-Roll
    - Sparrows Point…Better Than Ever, Undated; VHS (Box 20, Item 2)
    - Troubled Partners, Undated; VHS (Box 20, Item 18)
      Reel #1. Time-code burns.
    - Troubled Partners, Undated; VHS (Box 20, Item 19)
      Reel #2. Time-code burns.
    - Troubled Partners, Undated; VHS (Box 20, Item 20)
      Reel #3. Time-code burns.
    - Troubled Partnerships, Undated; VHS (Box 20, Item 21)
    - Troubled Partnerships, Undated; VHS (Box 20, Item 23)
    - Troubled Partnerships, Undated; VHS (Box 20, Item 24)
    - Troubled Partnerships, Undated; VHS (Box 20, Item 26)
      First Print.
    - Partners, 1996; VHS (Box 20, Item 28)
    - Stills, Undated; VHS (Box 20, Item 29)
      Reels 1 and 2. Burn-In Dub.
    - Stills, Undated; VHS (Box 20, Item 30)
      Reels 3 and 4. Burn-In Dub.
    - Pittsburgh, United Steelworkers, 1996-03-15; VHS (Box 21, Item 9)
      Reels 1-5. Window dubs.
    - San Diego, IRRA Panel and Interviews, 2004-01-04; VHS (Box 21, Item 11)
      Reels 1 and 2.
    - San Diego, IRRA Panel and Interviews, 2004-01-04; VHS (Box 21, Item 12)
      Reels 3 and 4.
    - San Diego, IRRA Panel and Interviews, 2004-01-04; VHS (Box 21, Item 13)
      Reels 5 and 6.
    - San Diego, IRRA Panel and Interviews, 2004-01-04; VHS (Box 21, Item 14)
      Reels 7 and 8.
    - San Diego, IRRA Panel and Interviews, 2004-01-04; VHS (Box 21, Item 15)
      Reels 9 and 10.
    - San Diego, IRRA Panel and Interviews, 2004-01-04; VHS (Box 21, Item 16)
      Reel 11.
    - ISG Steel, 2002-08-09; VHS (Box 21, Item 17)
      Window dub. Cleveland Works, OSV Studios. B-Rll.
    - ISG Steel Mill, 2002-10-10; VHS (Box 21, Item 18)
    - ISG, 2002-10-15; VHS (Box 21, Item 19)
    - USWA/BSF Compilation, 1998-10-19; VHS (Box 22, Item 1)
      Window Burn Ins. 1. USWA Camp Justice; 2. Rally and March; 3. Press Conference BSF; 4. Running Over; 5. Picket Line Shots.
    - Akron Ohio, Undated; VHS (Box 22, Item 2)
      Tapes #11-13. Time-Code Window.
    - Polaroid Archives and B-Roll, 1998-06-24; VHS (Box 22, Item 3)
      Time code burn-ins.
    - Polaroid Series 1, Undated; VHS (Box 22, Item 4)
      Reels 1 and 2. Time-Code Window.
    - Kennedy School/Cambridge, 1995-02-14; VHS (Box 22, Item 5)
      Reel 1 of 2. Interview/B-Roll. Burn-in.
    - Kennedy School/Cambridge, 1995-02-14; VHS (Box 22, Item 6)
      Reel 2 of 2. Interview/B-Roll. Burn-in.
    - Robert McKersie, 1996-04-16; VHS (Box 22, Item 7)
    - Robert McKersie, 1996-04-16; VHS (Box 22, Item 8)
    - Labor Notes Biennial Conference, 1999-04; VHS (Box 22, Item 9)
      April 23-25, 1999. Banquet.
    - Labor Notes Biennial Conference, 1999-04; VHS (Box 22, Item 10)
      April 23-25, 1999. Corporate Accountability Workshop.
    - Labor Notes Biennial Conference, 1999-04; VHS (Box 22, Item 11)
      April 23-25, 1999. Winning Better Contracts with Rank and File Power.
    - Labor Notes Biennial Conference, 1999-04; VHS (Box 22, Item 12)
      April 23-25, 1999. Cutting Globalization Down to Size.
    - 1989 Eastern Air Strike, 1999-11-06; VHS (Box 22, Item 13)
      Cleveland, Ohio
    - 24th Annual TDU Rank and File Convention, 1999-11-05; VHS (Box 22, Item 14)
      Teamsters Fighting Back. Cleveland, Ohio.
    - Hoffa Slate/Leedham Slate: IBT Teamsters Candidate Forum, Undated; VHS (Box 22, Item 15)
    - National Press Club, 2001-05-15; VHS (Box 22, Item 16)
    - In a New Direction: An Interview with Jerry Tucker, Undated; VHS (Box 22, Item 17)
    - Wilbur Ross Interview and B-Roll, 2004-02-26; VHS (Box 22, Item 18)
      New York City.
    - Cecil Roberts Speech, Undated; VHS (Box 22, Item 19)
    - National Press Club Lunch, 1999-11-19; VHS (Box 22, Item 20)
      1899-12-31T12:59:59+00:00
    - National Press Club, 2001-02-05; VHS (Box 22, Item 21)
    - Work Crisis, 1981-01-12; VHS (Box 22, Item 22)
      Transfer from 3/4.
    - ABC New Video Source, 1998-11-10; VHS (Box 22, Item 23)
    - Labor Conference Dunlop Hearings, Undated; VHS (Box 22, Item 24)
      1-7.
    - LTV News Footage, 2005-11; VHS (Box 22, Item 25)
      Transfer from DVCAM w/TC Window. Youngstown, Cleveland, D.C.
    - The Big Deal, Undated; VHS (Box 22, Item 26)
    - A New Generation, Undated; VHS (Box 22, Item 27)
    - LTV Steel, 2001; VHS (Box 22, Item 28)
      December 1-11, 2001. Television coverage from various stations, Cleveland, Ohio.
    - ABC New Video Source, 2001-11-26; VHS (Box 22, Item 34)
    - Saturn Project, Window Dubs, Reel 1-4, Undated; VHS (Box 1)
      Detroit, Rundell, and Bluestone
    - Saturn Project, Window Dubs, Reel 5-6, Undated; VHS (Box 1)
      Detroit, Don Ephlin
    - Saturn Plant/Nashville TC-Window Burn-In, 1993-08-26; VHS (Box 1)
      Reels 1-7
    - Stanley Update: The Struggle Continues - United Paperworkers International Union, Undated; VHS (Box 1)
    - Saturn Manufacturing Complex, Spring Hill, TN, Undated (Box 1)
      TC Window, GM B-Roll
  - III.f. Other Formats
    - Unions in Crisis, Undated; Open Reel Video tape (Box 12, Item 22)
      PAL. No.15929.
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, Undated; Open Reel Video tape (Box 12, Item 23)
      PAL. No.15934.
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; Open Reel Video tape (Box 23, Item 19)
      Duplication Master.
    - Unions in Crisis, Undated; Open Reel Video tape (Box 26, Item 1)
    - Unions in Crisis, Undated; Open Reel Video tape (Box 69, Item 1)
    - Hybrid VUE, 2007-03; DVD (Box 23, Item 17)
    - ION and VUE Production, 2007; DVD (Box 23, Item 18)
    - Rustbelt Phoenix, Undated; DVD (Box 23, Item 20)
      NTSC.
    - Rustbelt Phoenix, Undated; DVD (Box 23, Item 21)
      PAL.
    - Working Together: Saturn and the UAW, 1994; DVD (Box 23, Item 22)
    - Loose Bolts?, 1973; DVD (Box 23, Item 23)
    - Program N2391TP1, 1993-06-17; 1/2" Computer Tape (Box 26, Item 2)
    - Crisis Bargaining, Undated; 1/4" open reel audio tape (Box 52, Item 1)
      7" reel.
    - Struggling Unions A + B, Undated; Audio Cassette (Box 1)
    - Struggling Unions F, Undated; Audio Cassette (Box 1)
    - Rustbelt Phoenix Meeting, Undated; Audio Cassette (Box 1)
    - Saturn #1, Undated; Audio Cassette (Box 1)
    - Saturn 2, Undated; Audio Cassette (Box 1)
    - Troubled Partnerships B, Undated; Audio Cassette (Box 1)
    - Troubled Partnerships C, Undated; Audio Cassette (Box 1)
    - Troubled Partnerships D, Undated; Audio Cassette (Box 1)
    - Troubled Partnerships F, Undated; Audio Cassette (Box 1)